{
    "subject": "resource/Lais_Ribeiro",
    "predicate": "ontology/Person/height",
    "object": "185.42",
    "human_readable": "Lais Ribeiro's height is 185.42.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.837036669254303,
            "question": "Is Lais Ribeiro considered tall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8276942372322083,
            "question": "What is Lais Ribeiro's height?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6975037455558777,
            "question": "How tall is Lais Ribeiro in centimeters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6325271725654602,
            "question": "What might be some advantages of being Lais Ribeiro's height?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5536085367202759,
            "question": "How does Lais Ribeiro's height compare to the average height for women?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3891104459762573,
            "question": "Could Lais Ribeiro be a model?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14195887744426727,
            "question": "Are there any historical figures known for their height?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09568239003419876,
            "question": "Are there any sports where height is an advantage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0899258702993393,
            "question": "Can height be a determining factor in certain professions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07847125083208084,
            "question": "What factors might influence someone's height?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lais Ribeiro's height is 185.42.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2252_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can height be a determining factor in certain professions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2252_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any sports where height is an advantage?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2252_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical figures known for their height?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2252_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2252_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2252_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2252_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2252_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2252_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2252_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2252_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2252_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2252_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2252_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states that Lais Ribeiro's height is 6 feet 1 inch (1.85 m) or 180 cm. There isn't any mention of a height of 185.42."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nExplanation: The documents provide multiple sources with different information about Lais Ribeiro's height, including 5ft 11in (180 cm), 6 feet 1 inches, and 182 \u00d1\u0096n c\u00d0\u00b5nt\u00d1\u0096m\u00d0\u00b5tr\u00d0\u00b5\u00d1\u0095. However, none of these sources mention a height of 185.42."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide Lais Ribeiro\u2019s height as 6 feet 1 inch or 182 cm, not 185.42 cm."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}